ezmobilemy.com 2016-04-26

# Home

Privacy Policy

This website and the service are owned and operated by Provider, Ezmobile, and its subsidiaries or associates ('we', 'our' or 'us'). By using the website and/or the service, you consent to the collection and usage of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our website and service. This Privacy Policy is applicable to use of our website and/or our service, including but not limited to, all new facilities constituting any further expansion or improvement of our service.   

Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserved the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Should we have any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post it on this page. Your continued use of our website and/or service following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.   

Information We Collect

We collect and process 'personal information' (i.e. information that could be used to contact you, such as full name email address, phone number, postal address, MSISDN (mobile station integrated services digital network number), or 'demographic and usage information' (i.e. information that you submit, or that we collect, that is neither personal information nor financial information but necessary for the proper functioning and billing of our Service, such as the date regarding the start and end and the extension of your usage of the Service, the type of browser that you are using, web browsing patterns and IP address), in connection with the Service. We may pass on your personal information and/or demographic and usage information ('the information), to your carrier to secure collection of fees and charges. Such information collected by Provider may be stored and processed in the country in which Provider or its agents maintain facilities. By using the Service, you agree to any such transfer of Information outside of your country. The information will be deleted no later than six months after termination of your subscription and upon your request in written. Provider may store the Information beyond this date if that is required by law or contract.   

How We Use Your Information

We provide you an extensive collection of mobile entertainment via the Service. We will use your personal information to deliver the Service and for customer service. Your personal information is used by us to respond to your requests, process your transactions for the Service. Information about Service benefits, improvements, and promotions will be sent via text messaging or email from time to time. Unless you tell us not to, we may use your personal information to contact you about programs, products, features or services in which we believe you may be interested and/or other purposed disclosed. We may use your personal information to contact you regarding your use of the website and/or the service or changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Service (TOS), or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of the website and/or the service. In addition, we may use information collected about you to improve the content and navigation of our website and/or the service, or for other internal purposes.   

In addition to our service providers and third party contractors specified herein, we may also share your personal information with other third party marketers and business partners who may contact you regarding their products and services and who may want to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.    

If you would like to opt-out of our sharing of your personal information with those third party marketers and business partners for marketing purposes, indicate that we may not do so at the point where you give us such personal information. **If you change your mind later, you can send an e-mail to the address as communicated to you on the website and/or through our Services. Please take note that deletions of your personal information or changes in your preferences may not be effective immediately and will be effective for the purpose of managing future communications only.**   

We use demographic information for internal purposes and to help us administer the Service and interact with visitors to our website and/or the service. We may also share demographic information in the aggregate form with third parties to illustrate trends and patterns. Your demographic information may be used to personalize and customize the content of the Service for you and send you targeted ads based on keyword searches. We may also combine the information we collect with third parties or publicly available information.   

When you sign up for the Service or use other features of the Service, we collect your mobile telephone number and the identity of your mobile telephone service provider. Charges for the Service can be billed directly to your mobile telephone service account. By purchasing the Service, you consent to our providing your mobile telephone number to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include the carriers used to process the transaction.   

We may use third party contractors to help us operate our business, the Service and administer activities on our behalf, such as authorization of mobile telephone bill transactions, and may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes.   

If Provider is sold to, or merges with, another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets or bankruptcy event. We may also disclose your information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety of Provider or users of the Service.    

Cookies

To enhance your experience with our website and/or service, we may use cookies on the website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you become a customer and furnish the website with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.   

We use cookies to understand website usage and to improve the content and offerings on our websites. For instance, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our webpages (e.g., to recognize you when you return to our website). Certain areas of our websites can be accessed only in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content.   

**Adults Only**

**Neither the Service nor the Sites are intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any personal information submitted by users who have not reached the age of 18 years old.**   

Links

The websites may contain links to other web- or wapsites. Provider does not control such other web- and wapsites and is not responsible or liable for the availability thereof or the content, advertising, products or other materials contained on such sites. **Provider shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss incurred or suffered by any user in connection therewith. Your access and use of linked sites, including the content therein, is solely at your own risk.**   

**Security**

**Protecting your information is important to us. We implement a variety of industry standard security measures to protect the security of your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet and via mobile communications networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to do our best to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or through us.**   

Accessing Your Information 

Provider gives you the opportunity to review, edit, and/or remove personal information that you have provided to us. You can send an e-mail to the address that you can find on the website and state whether you want your information removed from our database, if you want to opt-out of communications from us or if you want to opt-out of communications from third party marketers or business partners. Deleting your information or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from Provider or third parties will delete the data only in our database for purposes of managing future communications from Provider and third parties. These deletions will not delete information already collected that may have already been shared with third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy. You will need to contact third parties that may contact you directly to delete your personal information that they may be using to contact you.   

Contact Us

Please contact us with any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy. This Privacy Policy was updated in June 2009.
